thecultureist.com 2013-11-01

# The Culture-ist Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes the policies and procedures of The Culture-ist (Culture-ist LLC) on the collection, use and disclosure of your information on [www.the cultureist.com](http://www.thecultureist.com/ "The Culture-ist") and the services, features, content or applications offered by The Culture-ist. The Culture-ist receives information about you from various sources, including:

  * If you register for the Site’s Daily or Weekly Email (your “Account”)
  * Your use of the Services generally
  * From third party websites and services

When you use the Services, you are consenting to the collection, transfer, repurposing, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

##### What information does The Culture-ist collect?

The Culture-ist collects information from you when you register on our site or subscribe to our newsletter.When registering on our site, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on [The Culture-ist](http://www.thecultureist.com/ "The Culture-ist"). Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to The Culture-ist and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

##### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

##### How do we protect your information?

The Culture-ist endeavors to protect Account information to ensure that it is kept private; however, we cannot guarantee the security of any account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time.

##### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

##### Third party links

****Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

##### Online Privacy Policy Only

****This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

##### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our website’s privacy policy.

##### Changes to our Privacy Policy

The Culture-ist may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information collected now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we collect or use information, we will notify you by posting updating this page or sending you an email. A user is bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Services after such changes have been first posted.

##### What If I Have Questions?

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy using the Services, please send a message to [anthony@thecultureist.com](mailto:anthony@thecultureist.com). We will make every effort to address and resolve your concerns.

_Effective date: September 1, 2011_  
_This policy was last modified on March 15, 2013_
